(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
Now, the Dick Launching Ceremony
is about to begin.
10, 9, 8...
The opening kicked off
with a few fireworks.
It is said to represent the letters SHO,
the symbol of lewdness.
3, 2, 1...
Eh? N-L-N-S?
So that is the answer you've chosen.
Senpai.
Now!
The New Hamedori-kun
Mass Outbreak Operation...
commence!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Engage!
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements,
rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate,
don't ever stop
Destroy it,
make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
Of the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
SHAVED ICE - CANDY APPLE
TAKOYAKI - DICK LAUNCHING CEREMONY
COTTON CANDY - SPONGE CAKE
QUESTION ABOUT THE NEW SEX LAW
What?
There are 60 million dicks
in Japan alone?!
That's insane!
It's the new dawn of Japan!
Ryoma must be thrilled!
QUESTION ABOUT NANASE KATAGIRI
You've got to be kidding me.
I heard she was XXX.
But she still has a XXX.
Well, that's a turn-on in its own right.
Whoa!
What's that?
Ariadne Protocol.
Engage!
They made their move.
Five Hamedori-kun are approaching!
They are heading to the port
while jamming our devices!
Just as Touka-sama reported.
All hands to battle stations.
The Stronghold Formation!
Ah!
That's the...
final defense formation designed for
the invasion of the anti-pervert forces.
Defend the Guillotine!
Capture the Magical Dick at all costs!
That is the true way...
to protect the daily life you love.
The things you truly want...
are really hard to get,
aren't they, senpai?
Hostile genitalia approaching,
overwhelming numbers!
They're all soaking wet.
Disperse!
Break through by blending in
with the swarm of Hamedori-kun.
It's a full-on dick!
I'll provide support.
And you, Tachibana-san?
To Nanase-chan!
Yes.
Leave it to me.
Switching radar to Dogfight mode.
Master Arm On!
This is the moment of truth.
It's all or nothing!
Let's do this!
Yeah.
It's time for the ring-entering ceremony.
I'm coming for you, Nanase!
How's the situation?
FS is moving to defend the Guillotine,
a crucial part of the new law,
and to secure the Anti-Copulation Force.
What about that thing
they have a warrant out for?
You mean the Magical Dick?
It certainly looked arousing,
but nothing more than that.
A Magical Dick, huh?
What a sight to see.
This is Null Base, I've reached the beach.
This isn't my forte,
but I'll cause a diversion.
A frontal attack?
What a reckless strategy!
So it's a cunnilingus strategy.
The enemy is trying to blend in
with the swarm of Hamedori-kun.
We'll suppress them before that happens.
They saw through it.
Damn it!
XXX dolls! Not on my watch!
Your little sister
will buy you some time.
Big brother!
Did it explode?
It's just a smoke bomb!
Learn something for once!
Got him! The Magical Dick!
What?
You say "dick,"
you mean "thick!"
You say "thick," you mean "dick!"
Another useless data
Instructor Rei,
what about the confiscated costume?
Just leave them on the patrol boat!
As expected, the enemy
has disguised themselves as Hamedori-kun.
Mozume.
I made it for this exact purpose.
An advanced version
of the XXX profile system.
The Magical Dick Tracking System.
Found it.
It's the Magical Dick.
That's him! Don't let him get away!
These guys...
But I have...
a military-grade combat suit treated with
a special DLO-0 material, the Hame Armor.
Pointless!
Worthless!
Flawless.
Unless you have a way
to win against these numbers.
Tsk!
It accurately tracks the Magical Dick,
regardless of its XXX state!
There's nowhere to hide your dick.
Dick?
T-The dick is...
There are too many dicks.
Are these landmines?
Then I just have to make it
a thousand dicks!
Dick-shaped landmines
mass-produced with a 3D printer.
I've named it: Spermines.
I knew you guys
would come after my dick.
This is Hamedori-kun and Magical Dick
Mass Outbreak Hame Operation!
We fell for their trap!
This is the cock
of a king who commands all.
Be sure to savor it!
Spit out your pre-cum!
I'm no longer afraid of my own dick,
as long as everyone accepts me.
T-The battlefield is full of dicks.
Point C! Unidentified flying objects
approaching from the rear!
It's UFD!
They're all over the place...
Are those flying dicks?!
Are you stupid?
Dicks can't fly...
The Dick-shaped Propeller Drone,
the Cock-Shock!
Go!
Point C is destroyed?!
The dicks have multiplied?
Not by sexual reproduction?
Wait.
Target acquired at Point B!
That chair...
I'm sure I saw it at Perverted Land, too
M-Man down! XXX down!
Aiming precisely at the XXX.
And with a ricochet at that!
Sniper eliminated.
Hame.
Oh, what a big bird.
It's Hamedori-kun.
The scientific name
is Aptenodytes Seiranhitoura.
There's no way I can beat someone so big.
It's karaoke for dinner tonight!
I think you mean Yu Lin Ji chicken.
I'm everyone's senpai.
A senpai can't...
run away in a place like this!
Oh my, is it night already?
Could it be... that I'm actually strong?
Points A, B, and C are all destroyed.
One target
has broken through the security gate,
and is approaching the port.
Stop them! At all costs!
I hear you!
Environmental destruction feels so good!
Now's our chance.
Go for it!
Tachibana-san.
Deploy Squad 3, with the fewest casualties,
to the bay area.
We can still win this...
Wait, another one is approaching.
An ambush?!
Hame!!!
Don't underestimate me.
Rei-chan.
Hinami... Why?
Sorry,
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
But...
W-Wait, Hinami, I can't fight you.
But I have to.
Because I'm a senpai.
This is for Tachibana-kun
and the others.
Tachibana?
You said Tachibana?!
Oops.
So he is the leader
of the Anti-Copulation Force?
The owner of the Magical Dick?
What are you doing?
Tch, to lose to a measly dick!
I can't leave it to you guys anymore.
I'm putting FS under SHO's command.
W-What?
Round up the useless ones!
Assign them to defend the Guillotine ship!
B-But if we focus all our forces
without having the enemy located, we'll...
- be vulnerable in a close-range fight!
- Shut up!
Do you want FS to be disbanded?
Hurry up and get ready!
We're setting sail.
Open the sluice gate!
Big sister.
Please look.
The Guillotine ship is setting sail.
The ship will now penetrate
to the designated sea area,
where the ceremony will reach its climax!
Along with the execution
of the Anti-Copulation Force's ringleader,
Nanase Katagiri.
Lewd Sex will spread
throughout the country.
Nukitashi.
I've been waiting for you.
Darling.
Hame.
So, what should I call you?
Nekobana-kun?
Or rather, Junnosuke Tachibana-kun?
You're so stubborn, darling.
Since you had the King Cock,
you should've had some fun with it
You'll lose to me again.
Want to give it a try?
I'm not the same person I was then.
The flowers on the table
are patiently waiting,
but the wait will soon be over.
With a drawn blade,
shall we now exchange sweet nothings?
Such a cool line!
I'm not done yet!
Dual wielding?!
It's a new weapon forged from a special
D10-O material to tear out ass hole.
The Chrysanthemum Blade, my trump card.
You want to do anal, right!?
Penetrator pierces through the XXX!
Chrysanthemum Blade tears the anus.
This is the famous
"king and rook fork" formation!
You made something dirty just for me.
I'm so happy.
Take this!
This intense attack is making me
look forward to the sex later.
You don't understand anything.
You can't have intercourse without love!
Love is something that comes after intercourse.
The alphabet proves it.
Shut up, I'm Japanese.
Love comes before any words.
I wonder about that.
I've been waiting for this moment.
I can't pull it out.
It's the 21st century.
A toy like a rusty Japanese sword
from hundreds of years ago,
can it compete with a modern,
extra-thick vibrator?
No way.
I've got you.
It's over.
Just kidding.
What?!
I already told you before.
I'm much better at groundwork.
Trump card should be saved for last, right?
Show me how long you can last.
So big!
I've been waiting...
for my fated dick.
Go for it.
Use that huge, thick, hard cock,
stir my XXX into a mess.
Become the one
who rules over sex, the Sex Emperor.
And you'll reign supreme over the world.
That's right.
Flaunt this dick
and make them understand my might!
Alright.
I'll do as you wish.
That's more like it.
Better savor it!
This is my...
Magical Dick!
Fire!
This is just fake cum!
I'm an expert at finishing on my own!
I'm getting serious now-
Your perversion and my stubbornness.
The one that's truly hard and strong...
is me!
So you've finally gathered, you slowpokes.
Maritime security!
Board the small craft, now!
What's with that face?
Act like the pawn you are!
In the end, we're just...
We've finally arrived.
This is the designated drop-off point
for Fumino-chan, right?
Yes.
The mission entrusted to me
by Tachibana-san,
I will get it done.
PURE VIRGIN
I've come to save you, comrade.
Jun.
This chain...
It can only be undone with sex, huh...
What a detestable thing!
Why?
Why did you come to save me?
I've come to save my comrade.
You can use this chaos
to escape the island!
Hurry up and run.
I won't run away.
Never again.
Why?
If we had Fumino,
we could have crushed the ordinance.
It's meaningless without you, Nanase.
NLNS is a team for
getting you and me home safely.
Damn it.
Nanase, so you still remember.
Everything from the past.
Then why?
If it's going to eat you up with guilt,
then it's better that you don't know.
That's why this time...
I wanted to create a place for you.
I wanted to become your true comrade.
Next time for sure,
no matter what, I'll be your ally.
I've always wanted to say that.
Thanks to you,
Asane and I've made friends.
No, not just us.
Wata-chan.
Misaki.
Fumino.
No one is alone anymore.
Even the FS, our enemy.
In a sense,
I realized they're the same as us.
Nanase.
I was saved by you,
my first love,
twice on this island.
So let me say it again.
I'm truly sorry
for what I put you through back then.
I will never make you suffer again.
I will fight everything
that makes you suffer.
Jun.
Tachibana-kun.
You are the one...
who understands me for who I am.
Yeah.
This time for sure, I won't regret it.
It's fine, Tachibana-kun.
Nanase, this...
Yeah.
I can finally accept it.
Nanase.
Eh? Are you okay?
My thing is kinda intense.
Your womb might fall just by putting it in.
I'm fine.
I've already fallen for you.
So happy.
I'm actually having sex with you.
Is that the girl?
Are you here for the handover?
I don't know how much
she's worth in this state,
but leave the rest to us.
My apologies.
But I'm not coming.
What?
I know the anus inside and out.
Do you understand what that means?
You are our bargaining chip.
The area has been cleared.
So you've come all this way to see me.
Senpai.
I've come to save you.
Well, that's wonderful.
The threads I weave
will be your chilling cage.
A quiet space where tension dances.
Come now,
shall we see if you can still dance
once your body is torn to pieces?
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder,
have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me